<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Episodes on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://kind-joliot-1699fe.netlify.com/episodes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Episodes on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kind-joliot-1699fe.netlify.com/episodes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast 65: A Big Brand&#39;s Small Start to a Successful Localization Program</title>
      <link>https://kind-joliot-1699fe.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-65-a-big-brands-small-start-to-a-successful-localization-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kind-joliot-1699fe.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-65-a-big-brands-small-start-to-a-successful-localization-program/</guid>
      <description>In this episode of Globally Speaking, Oleksandr Pysaryuk, Localization Manager at Achievers, shares how he got into localization management, the success factors involving in managing a localization program, and how to boost employee satisfaction.

Having playback issues? Try the alternate player of this episode below:

About Oleksandr Pysaryuk Oleksandr Pysaryuk is the Localization Manager at Achievers, provider of the cloud-based Employee Success Platform. At Achievers, he is in charge of all things related to localization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast 64: Proving the ROI of Localization</title>
      <link>https://kind-joliot-1699fe.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-64-proving-the-roi-of-localization/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kind-joliot-1699fe.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-64-proving-the-roi-of-localization/</guid>
      <description>Chris Englund, Senior Manager of Localization at HubSpot, shares his insights and experience on how a well-known global B2B brand handles localization. He provides details about HubSpot’s successful localization program and talks about how your localization approach can drive value and how you can prove program ROI.

Having playback issues? Try the alternate player of this episode below:

About Chris Englund In his role as Localization Manager at HubSpot, Chris ensures that inbound marketing content and education accompany their offerings as they strengthen roots in non-English markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast 63: Making the Most of Localization Events and Conferences</title>
      <link>https://kind-joliot-1699fe.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-63-making-the-most-of-localization-events-and-conferences/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kind-joliot-1699fe.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-63-making-the-most-of-localization-events-and-conferences/</guid>
      <description>The months of September through November mark the season of conferences. In Globally Speaking episode 63, we discuss the various events around the world, why they are valuable and how to make the most of them. Hope to see you at an event soon!

Having playback issues? Try the alternate player of this episode below:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>